克劳伦斯与低语者
编剧：史蒂文·莫法特
停下 停下
Stop it! Stop it!
停止低语
Stop whispering!
让我清静一下
Leave me alone!
你们不是真的
You are not real!
我知道你们不是真的
I know you are not real.
你们只是我脑中的声音
You are just voices inside my head.
别再烦我了
Leave me alone!
你们想要什么
What do you want from me, em?
博士
The Doctor.
你们在说什么 我不明白
What are you talking about? I don't understand.
你想活吗
Do you want to live?
你们能救我
You can save me?
我们能给你信息
We can give you information.
这些符号 你要记住它们
These symbols, you will memorize them.
我不能
I don't...
它们的意义和目的现在都在你脑中
Their meaning and purpose is now within your mind.
你要把这信息传达给蜥蜴侦探
You well give this information to reptile detective.
你们是什么人
What kind of men are you?
我们不是人 我们是高等智能
We are not men, we are The Intelligence.
我们知晓一切时间与空间
All of time and space is known to us.
这能救我的命吗
Will this save me, huh?
我明天还会被绞死吗
Will I still hang tomorrow?
你会得到赦免
A pardon will be yours.
免于绞索之苦
The rope will not.
你们最终会放过我吗
Will you finally leave me alone?
你会活的很久
You will live a long life.
但是你将永远不得安眠
Except you will always have such trouble sleeping.
不 不
No! No!
请你们放过我
You will leave me alone.